<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on My Projects</title>
    <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on My Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 21:11:57 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://snipem.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/monako/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 21:11:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/monako/README/</guid>
      <description>monako    
 A less opinionated document aggregator and publisher. Easier to use and to adapt than Antora, Hugo, JBake and the likes.
 Purpose Monako abstracts the complexity of collecting documentation from a configurable amount of Git repositories (origins).
Monako uses Hugo as a static site generator but hides it to the user. It also uses the great Hugo Book Theme which I forked at Monako Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/CONTRIBUTE/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 19:57:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/CONTRIBUTE/</guid>
      <description>Contribute Upload to PIP Manual on how to upload to PIP
This will only work for me as the maintainer:
make dist  Twine uses the global config file in $HOME/.pypirc
Setup py Example setup.py
AutoPep autopep8 &amp;ndash;max-line-length 999 -i commute_tube/commute_tube.py</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-fandom/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 13:19:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-fandom/README/</guid>
      <description>alfred-fandom Simple workflow for Fandom
Requirements jq
Install with brew install jq</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-spotify/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 20:50:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-spotify/README/</guid>
      <description>Alfred-Spotify Alfred-Spotify searches for tracks (Keyword: sp) and albums (spa).
Download See Releases.
Setup You will have to setup Spotify API tokens as SPOTIFY_ID and SPOTIFY_SECRET environment variables in the imported workflow. You can obtain the tokens from this site.
Currently the default action is to call a custom made Bose Soundtouch script of mine to enqueue the song to the device. You may change the default behaviour to just open the url, like it is currently bound to the alt action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/maniacforum/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 19:17:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/maniacforum/README/</guid>
      <description>Maniac Forum UI  
Download Downloads für diverse Betriebssysteme finden sich in den Releases
Oder alternativ go get github.com/snipem/maniacforum.
Hilfe Kontext-Steuerung &amp;lt;Tab&amp;gt; - Fokus-Wechsel auf Boards, Threads, Unterthreads und Nachrichten ↑ ↓ - Zur Auswahl im aktuellen ausgewählten Menü ← → - Auswahl des Boards a - Auf Nachricht im Standard-Browser antworten ? - Hilfsseite q - Beenden 0-9 - Links im Standard-Browser öffnen  Globale Steuerung  j - Nächster Unterthread k - Vorheriger Unterthread u - Nächster ungelesener Unterthread z - Nächster Thread J - Nächster Thread K - Vorheriger Thread  Gelesen / Ungelesen Status von Beiträgen maniacforum speichert den Lesestatus von Beiträgen standardmäßig unter $HOME/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-dazn/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 13:30:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-dazn/README/</guid>
      <description>Alfred-DAZN Description Simple DAZN Schedule listing for Parsing through Alfred</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/psnprices/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 20:25:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/psnprices/README/</guid>
      <description>gameprices  
Command line tool for alerting price drops in the Sony PlayStation Network (PSN) and the Nintendo Eshop.
Description The Sony Entertainment Network (SEN) uses CIDs to identify items in it&amp;rsquo;s catalogue. In order to alert you on the desired price of an SEN you need the CID. Use your Browser (cid GET parameter in URL) or this script (&amp;ndash;search) to retrieve the CID.
In order to check the price of an item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-deezer/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 23:48:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/alfred-deezer/README/</guid>
      <description>Alfred-Deezer Alfred-Deezer searches for tracks (Keyword: h) and albums (da).
Download See Releases.
Setup for Development See deezer-cli on how to setup deezer-cli which is included to the workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/README/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 17:23:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/README/</guid>
      <description>commute-tube  
commute-tube is your friend on your daily commute. It will download videos of your interest to your USB pen by night so that you&amp;rsquo;re able to watch the program in bus or train. It is basically a configurable wrapper for youtube-dl.
I made this tool because I was getting a new job with a daily commute via train attached. On that train ride no cellular network nor wifi was available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/psnprices/CONTRIBUTING/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 17:28:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/psnprices/CONTRIBUTING/</guid>
      <description>Get test coverage py.test \ --tx socket=192.168.178.87:9999 \ --pep8 \ --spec \ --instafail \ --cov=gameprices \ --cov-report html \ gameprices/test  Enable paralell tests
-n 8  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/LICENSE/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 15:42:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snipem.github.io/docs/commute/LICENSE/</guid>
      <description>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 3, 29 June 2007  Copyright (C) 2007 Free Software Foundation, Inc. http://fsf.org/ Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.
 Preamble  The GNU General Public License is a free, copyleft license for software and other kinds of works.
The licenses for most software and other practical works are designed to take away your freedom to share and change the works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>